Shredding onto video. Leap day 2000.
An Extremely Goofy Movie is a animation, family,
comedy film directed by Douglas McCarthy.
It's all extreme sports and a life of freedom as Max sets off for college -- but Goofy misses Max
so much he loses his job and goes to finish college alongside Max and his friends.
But as Goofy tries to get closer to Max, both must go to the
extreme to learn how to live their own lives together.
Goofy (voice), played by Bill Farmer.
Max (voice), played by Jason Marsden.
Bradley Uppercrust / Unemployment Lady / Chuck  (voice), played by Jeff Bennett.
Pete (voice), played by Jim Cummings.
Tank (voice), played by Brad Garrett.
Beret Girl (voice), played by Vicki Lewis.
Disney's An Extremely Goofy Movie is a 2000 American animated sports comedy film distributed by Walt Disney
Home Video, produced by Walt Disney Television Animation, and directed by Douglas McCarthy.
It is a sequel to the 1995 film A Goofy Movie and the finale
to the 1992 television series Goof Troop.
The film was released on Blu-ray as a Disney Movie Club
exclusive alongside A Goofy Movie on April 23, 2019.
The film received mostly positive reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of skateboarding, sports,
parent child relationship, cartoon, college.
The tone is lighthearted.